- 你覺得戴倫賈維怎樣？  - CBS的？
-What do you think of Darren Jarvis?  -At CBS?
他想要我當記者
He wants me to be a correspondent.
別浪費時間
It's not worth your time.
那MSNBC的葛利費雪呢？
What about Greer Fisher, at MSNBC?
繼續寫作，電視當副業  你當主播太可惜了
Stick to writing, do TV on the side.  You're more than a talking head.
- 《頭條報導》如何？  - 《頭條報導》？
-How about Slugline?  -What's Slugline?
如果《政治新聞網》想僱用我  你覺得呢？
If I said Politico wanted to hire me,  what would you say?
這倒是讓我很感興趣
I would say that that piques my interest.
不出六個月，  《頭條報導》會成為  一年半前的《政治新聞網》
Six months from now, Slugline will be  what Politico was a year and half ago.
《政治新聞網》的人都會看
Everyone at Politico reads it
因為《頭條報導》的特報  比他們快
because Slugline's breaking stories  before they are.
我怎麼沒聽過這份雜誌
I wonder why I've never heard of it.
人人是自由撰稿
Everyone's a free agent.
不論人在何處  都能寫出心中想法
And they write whatever they want,  wherever they are.
大多人用手機撰稿
Most people write from their phones.
如果他們能提供自由與曝光度
Well, if freedom and exposure  are what they're offering,
你該和他們會會面
I would say that is a meeting worth taking.
翰默史密事件爆發了
This Hammerschmidt thing is blowing up.
我覺得他會被開除
I think he might get fired.
這裏有上千條推文…
There's got to be a thousand tweets here...
有人捍衛我，有人詆毀我
People defending me, people trashing me.
還有人寫標籤說，喬伊加油
There's even a hashtag, GoZoe.
嘿！
Hey!
- 不能留下線索  - 我全部的連絡人都在裏面
-We mustn't leave any trails.  -All of my contacts were in there.
那你該去找新的連絡人了
Then it's time for you  to get some new contacts.
別擔心，我會給你手機  其實我會給你兩支
Don't worry. I'll get you a phone.  I'll get you two, in fact.
一個工作用，一個拿來玩遊戲  下午就會送來
One for work and a burner for play.  Expect them this afternoon.
還有…加油，喬伊
And... Go, Zoe.
- 記者？  - 對
-The reporter?  -Yes.
就這一次？
Just this once?
我不確定
I'm not sure.
她能給我們什麼？
What does she offer us?
必要時她可以為我們傳話  目前為止，她很有幫助
A mouthpiece, when we need one.  She's been very useful so far.
- 她要什麼？  - 門路
-What does she want?  -Access.
地位
A seat at the table.
聽起來她佔有優勢
Sounds like she's getting  the better side of the bargain.
我能控制她
She can be controlled.
你確定嗎？
Are you sure?
會的，我保證
She can. I promise you.
好吧，既然你這麼說
Okay, if you say so.
只要你要我結束…
The moment you want me to end it...
我知道，法蘭斯
I know, Francis.
我該準備上班了
I should get ready for work.
你好…
Hey...
我以為你晚點才會進辦公室
I didn't think you'd be in until later.
這是你今天的行程表  這是你這周的計劃表
This is your agenda for the day.  Here's your schedule for the rest of the week.
這些是需要核准或簽名的文件
These are papers  that need to be approved or signed.
這裏是你委員會會議的提綱
Over here are your one-sheets  for committee meetings
還有接下來的立法行動簡報
and briefs on upcoming legislative action.
我交代艾希莉了  在你找到新人前，她可以代班
I filled Ashley in.  She can cover until you find a replacement.
克裏絲汀娜
Christina.
怎麼了？
What?
謝謝
Thank you.
把這些整理好
For getting all this in order.
如果你對桌上的文件有疑問  艾希莉可以打電話給我
Ashley can call me ifyou have any questions  about what's on your desk.
- 他到了沒？  - 我安排他到你辦公室
-He here yet?  -I put him in your office.
馬帝史皮奈拉  是教師工會的陳情代表
Marty Spinella. Head lobbyist for  the teachers union.
他恨不得扭斷我的頭、剝我的皮
He wants to rip my head off  and peel it like an orange.
為什麼？因為我對他說謊  但是我有什麼選擇呢？
Why? Because I lied to him.  But what choice did I have?
說了真相就別想談話了
When the truth would have ended  the conversation before it began?
- 我會回電  - 馬帝
-I'll call you back.  -Marty.
法蘭，你撒謊？
You fucking lied, Frank?
你當著我的面撒謊？
No, no, no. You lie to my fucking face?
- 馬帝，我沒撒謊  - 什麼意思？
-Marty, I did not lie.  -What do you mean you did not?
我們花了整整一個週末  逐條討論這個提案
We spent a whole weekend in that room  poring over this bill line by line.
根本沒提到勞資談判
And nowhere did it say anything  about collective bargaining.
冷靜點，坐下  我們來討論吧
Let's calm down and sit down.  And we will discuss this.
我會解釋一切  開誠佈公地說
I will explain everything that's going on  and we will talk it out.
- 談多久都沒關係  - 不用了
-No matter how long it takes.  -No. No more.
這會是簡短的會議
This is gonna be a very short meeting.
因為只有兩條路可走
'Cause only one of two things  are going to happen.
一來就是你現在擔保  刪除那條修正案
Either you assure me right now  that amendment is out,
或是我現在就走出去  展開炮轟
or I am walking out that door  and I am gonna start launching missiles.
我本來就不打算  將那條修正案留在提案裏
The amendment was never intended  to stay in the bill.
只是籌碼而已
It's just there for leverage. That's all.
你威脅要刪除  工會學區的聯邦補助？
You threaten to cut  federal funding from union school districts?
法蘭，那可不是撲克牌籌碼  那是天殺的髒彈
That's not a poker chip, Frank,  that's a goddamn dirty bomb.
修正案不會留在提案裏
Look, the amendment  is not staying in the bill.
我只需要你和我  一起處理成績標準
I just need you to  work with me on performance standards.
成績標準？
Performance standards?
你開什麼玩笑？  你說過已經刪除了
Are you fucking kidding me?  You agreed that they were already out.
- 法蘭，不能放回去  - 馬帝…
-You can't just put it back in now, Frank.  -Marty, look...
我得維護我的名聲
I have a reputation to uphold.
你在蓋弗尼玩你的鬼桃子時
I am the one that made the union reps  stay here for you
是我說服工會代表在這等你
while you're in Gaffney  playing with your fucking Peachoid.
- 馬帝…  - 現在說
-Marty...  -You tell me right now,
會不會刪除那個修正案？
is that amendment in or out?
馬帝，這還有妥協之處  我們可以找到的
There is a middle ground here, Marty.  We just have to find it.
我把這當作是不會
I take that as a no.
好吧
Okay.
馬帝，別打明知會輸的仗
Marty, do not start a war  you know you're gonna lose.
你耍我，我就反擊
You fuck me, I fuck back.
史坦普！
Stamper!
馬帝和我向來合作愉快
Marty and l  have a good working relationship.
或許該說曾經
Or used to.
看得出他有脾氣
You could see he has a temper,
但我通常能消他火氣  跟他說理
but I can usually cut through that  and reason with him.
但我可能逼人太甚了  這讓人有點擔心
But I may have pushed him too far.  Which is worrisome.
朋友會是最可怕的敵人
Friends make the worst enemies.
- 怎麼樣？  - 你聽到什麼？
-How'd it go?  -What'd you hear?
- 一堆髒話  - 大致就是這樣了
-A lot of fucks.  -Well, that pretty much says it.
我們來想想…
Let's think this through...
- 還得開民主黨全委會領導會議  - 什麼？
-No, we've got the DNC leadership meeting.  -What?
本來可以不用參加  但是柏許剛推給我們
I'd say you could skip it,  but Birch just dumped it on us.
- 何時？  - 12分鐘後在這裏
-When?  -It's here. In 12 minutes.
為什麼不是民主黨全委會總部？
Why here and not the DNC headquarters?
民主黨全委會正在修建  要善用綠能源
The DNC is doing renovations,  they're gonna be green-energy efficient.
真會運用黨基金
That's a charming use of party funds.
我們剛搬來這裏三個月
We've only been in this space  about three months.
酷
It's cool.
和《先軀報》不太像吧？
Not exactly The Herald, is it?
- 你去過那些辦公室嗎？  - 有
-Have you been to those offices?  -Yes.
真讓人想切腕
Wrist-slitting was in order.
還有誰誘惑過你？
So, who else is courting you?
- 一些人  - 你是說大家
-A few people.  -You mean everyone.
今早是有許多電郵…
There were a lot of emails this morning...
一點也不令人驚訝
That's not surprising.
你現在正紅  大家都對你感興趣
You're having a moment,  people are interested.
我是其中一個
I'm one of them.
但我對一件事的興致  只有八分鐘
But if eight minutes passes on anything,  I get bored.
八分鐘後，我可能對你感到厭倦  除非你讓我保持興致
In eight minutes, I could be bored with you.  Unless you keep me interested.
我覺得你辦得到
I think you can,
我覺得你在這裏  也可以讓其他人不斷關注你
and I think this is the place for you  to keep the rest of the world interested, too.
這是你的決定，我不會逼你
It's your call. I won't chase you.
我非常感興趣…
I'm definitely tempted...
盡量走走看看
Take as long as you want to look around.
寫電郵告訴我你的薪資  我會回信談價
Email me your figure.  I'll call you back with a counter.
這是我們的首要區域  俄亥俄、佛羅里達和賓州
This is our top priority.  Ohio, Florida and Pennsylvania.
我們全部要拿下  否則沃克只能當一任總統
We need all of them  or Walker's a one-term president.
他挑馬修擔任競選夥伴  就是為了拿下賓州
Pennsylvania is why he picked Matthews  as a running mate.
但是我們現在得找替代人選  補選在今年11月
But now we have to find a replacement.  The special election is this November.
派翠西亞惠特克是  民主黨全委會的主席
Patricia Whittaker. DNC chair.
是少數有頭腦的人
A rare example of someone  whose head is in the game
而不是用屁股思考
instead of up their backside.
在這圈，有能力的人極為罕見
Competence is such an exotic bird  in these woods
我極為欣賞有能力的人
that I appreciate it whenever I see it.
這也影響到眾議院
Now, this also affects the House.
新州長會監督重劃選區
The new Governor will oversee redistricting.
我們若在這失去席位
We lose seats here,
就可能在華府失去多數
that means we could lose  our majority in Washington.
共和黨全委會支持  匹茲堡前任市長傑克史沃佛特
Well, the RNC is backing Jack Swofford,  ex-mayor of Pittsburgh.
他擁有全州知名度  競選機制完全到位…
He's got state-wide name recognition and  campaign machinery in place...
三個月已過  我們還沒找到匹敵的人選
It's been three months  and we don't have dick.
司法部長班普魯克呢？
What about the A.G.? Ben Pluckett?
班將重心放在  2014年的參議院選舉
No, Ben's got his eyes set  on the Senate in '14.
但是他去年搞砸性犯罪提案  所以他會輸
Yeah, which he'll lose because  he botched a sex offender sting last year.
- 還可以找麥克哈倫  - 他78歲了
-Well, there's always McHolland.  -He's 78.
上次他任職是卡特當總統時？
When's the last time he held office?  When Carter was president?
雷根，不過差不多
Reagan, but same difference.
他有尊嚴、份量
Well, he has dignity. He has gravitas.
若要找人替代馬修…
I mean, if you need someone  to fill Matthews' shoes...
沒人可取代吉姆馬修  所以我們別試了
You can't fill Jim Matthews' shoes.  So we shouldn't even try.
我們需要新面孔
We need a fresh face.
這州沒什麼人才
The state has a weak bench.
那我們就從現任國會議員  一個一個地看
Well, let's go through all  the sitting Congressmen one by one,
看是否有人脫穎而出
and see if anybody  sticks out from the crowd.
好吧，我這裏有名單
All right. I got the list right here.
好吧，開始
Okay. Go ahead.
賓州第一選區的彼得魯索
Pennsylvania's first district, Peter Russo.
劃掉，他不夠好  沒經驗，能力一般
Cross him off. He's no good.  No experience. No chops.
好吧，繼續  第二選區的關多林皮爾斯
Okay, moving on.  Second district, Gwendolyn Pierce.
關太多爭議  對墮胎議題直言不諱…
Gwen's too controversial.  Very vocal on abortion...
- 卡羅琳呢？  - 她很好
-And, Caroline?  -She's good.
- 孩子們好嗎？  - 你問他們四個？
-Yeah? How're the boys?  -All fuckin' four of them?
你填飽四張嘴試試
You feed 'em.
手機裏有照片嗎？
You got any pictures? On your phone?
拜託，彼得，別說廢話了  造船廠的事要怎麼辦？
Come on. Let's cut the shit, Pete, will ya?  What are we gonna do about the shipyard?
基地重組與關閉辦了聽證會  他們要求關閉
BRAC had their hearing.  They slated it for closing.
你那時為何不作證？  這攸關一萬兩千人的工作
Yeah, and why didn't you testify?  We're talking 12,000 jobs here.
保羅，我束手無策  大家想關閉造船廠
My hands were tied, Paul.  People wanted it closed.
- 我當時壓力很大  - 是誰施壓？
-I was under a lot of pressure.  -From who?
高層的人，我無能為力
People high up the food chain.  There's nothing I could do.
少來，你回基地重組與關閉  去和國防部談
That's bullshit. You go back to BRAC.  You talk to the DOD.
去和海軍部長談，做點事…
You talk to the Secretary of the Navy.  You do something...
- 不可能的  - 為什麼？
-It's not gonna happen.  -Okay, why not?
我說了，這是政治
I told you, it's political.
好吧，那我要回造船工業會
Okay, so I'm supposed to go back to  the Shipbuilder's Association
說什麼呢？
and say what now, exactly?
說他們失業  是因為彼得魯索在搞政治？
That they're out of work  because Pete Russo's playing politics?
天哪，彼得
I mean, Jesus, Pete.
是我們支持你選上的
We're the ones who got you  fuckin' elected in the first place.
現在你卻背叛我們？
Now you're gonna turn your back on us?
你該離開了
You should go.
你說真的？
Seriously?
我才剛到，你就要踢我走？
I just got here. You're kickin' me out now?
我在和你說話
Hey, I'm fuckin' talkin' to you.
我以為我們是童年至交
I thought we grew up together.
但是這個  坐在那張大桌後面的傢伙
But this guy, sitting behind his big desk,
我完全不認識了
I don't even know who the fuck he is.
那個走投無路
Where's the Pete Russo  who knew how to throw a punch
知道怎麼反抗的彼得魯索  到哪裏了？
when his back was against the wall?
那傢伙才是我朋友
That guy was my friend.
全國所有教師？  在學期結束前一個月？
Every teacher in the country?  A month before school ends?
他不需要所有教師  只要15、20州就好
He doesn't need all of them.  Fifteen, 20 states. That's all.
美國教師聯盟  和國家教育協會向來不合
But the AFT and the NEA  can't agree on anything.
你低估了馬帝史皮奈拉
You underestimate Marty Spinella.
那我們的目標是誰？
So which one do we target?
國家教育協會勝算較大
We have a better chance with the NEA.
恰克史羅恩會上鉤嗎？
You think Chuck Sloan will bite?
合作，我們就保護你的人  拉抬你的地位
Cooperate, we give your people protection  and a place at the banquet.
跟我們作對，我們就毀了你
Fight us, we break you.
他會上鉤，打電話給他
He'll bite. Get him on the phone.
現在2點多了
It's after 2:00.
史皮奈拉可能會動員  美國史上
Spinella's potentially mobilizing  the largest teachers' strike
規模最大的教師罷工  沒人睡得著
in United States history. Nobody's sleeping.
我現在就打電話給他
I'll call him right now.
抱歉，我們太大聲了嗎？
I'm sorry. Are we being too loud?
有點
A little.
- 你在忙什麼？  - 藝廊有一堆事要忙
-What are you working on?  -The gala. There's so much to do.
- 南茜寄給你我的清單沒？  - 寄了
-Did Nancy send you my list?  -She did.
你覺得如何？
And what'd you think?
很棒的清單，謝謝你邀請他們
It's a good list. Thanks for inviting them.
出了什麼事？
Is something wrong?
這和瑞米提出的數字  還有很大差距
It's still not anywhere near  what Remy brought to the table.
法蘭斯，善可工業提出150萬
SanCorp offered 1.5 million, Francis.
我算了金額  我們只籌到50萬
I'm adding up the numbers  and we're only at half a million.
- 我連絡到恰克了  - 等一下
-I got Chuck on the phone.  -ln a minute.
我能多打電話…
I can make more calls...
能籌到150萬？
Enough to raise 1.5 million?
至少能讓我們更接近這數字
Well, I can at least get us closer.
我要睡了
I'm going to bed.
別動這裏的東西
Don't move any of this around.
克萊兒…是我們一起決定  要拒絕瑞米
Claire... We made the decision  to turn Remy down.
沒人強迫你  我以為我們對此沒意見
No one forced you.  I thought we were okay on this.
你說得對
You're right.
晚安，法蘭斯
Good night, Francis.
這是亞當，請留言
This is Adam. Leave a message.
亞當，是我  我知道很晚了，但是…
Hi, Adam, it's me. I know it's late, but...
我只是打電話來  再次謝謝你的照片
Well, I was really just calling to thank you  again for the photographs.
我相信在拍賣會時會大賣
I'm sure they're gonna be  a big hit at the auction.
希望你一切都好
Hope you're well.
我相信在拍賣會時會大賣
I'm sure they're gonna be  a big hit at the auction.
希望你一切都好
Hope you're well.
翰默史密先生，請往這走
Right this way, Mr. Hammerschmidt.
他到了
He's here.
午安，湯姆
Good afternoon, Tom.
律師？
Legal?
你說了還是沒說？
Did you say it or didn't you?
讓我回答你  和所有提出這個問題的人…
To you and to anyone who asks...
是的，我說了
Yes, I did.
我們真的需要他們嗎？
Do we really need them?
你若不對抗，我就不需要
Not unless I should expect a fight.
你不需要
You shouldn't.
給我們一點時間
Give us a few moments.
這和你怎麼罵她無關
It's not what you called her.
而是你辭退她了
It's that you let her leave the building.
我知道怎麼經營報社  瑪格莉特
I know how to run a paper, Margaret.
報社員工不受我控制  我就不知道要怎麼經營了
What I don't know how to do is run a paper  staffed with people I can't control.
她真的不受控？
Was she really out of control?
就我的理解  她只是拒絕新職位
To my understanding,  she simply turned down a new position.
是她的態度  她拒絕新職位的態度
It's her attitude.  It's the way she turned it down.
你想過問她想做什麼嗎？
Did you think to ask her  what she'd rather do instead?
我的工作是  迎合我所有員工的需求…
Is it my job to pander  to all my employees' wants...
是我的員工
My employees.
如果他們有你所沒有的能力
And if they have something to offer  that you don't,
那就是你的工作
yes, it is your job.
湯姆，我們談過這了
We've been through this, Tom.
報社的營運虧損  我們需要喬伊這樣的人才…
The paper's operating at a loss.  We need people like Zoe...
我非常清楚我們的虧損  瑪格莉特
I'm very aware of  how much we're hurting, Margaret.
人力縮編、發行量大減
Staff reductions, dip in circulation,
每個資遣員工的臉  和每個失去的訂戶
each one of those faces  and every subscriber we lose,
都讓我夜不成眠
they keep me awake at night.
現在我…我不談生意面的事
Now l...  I won't argue the business side of things.
我沒這資格  這也不是我的專業領域
It's neither my place nor my area of expertise.
但是要知道
But know this,
喬伊邦斯、推特、部落格
Zoe Barnes, Twitter, blogs,
氾濫的媒體，全都膚淺極了
enriched media, they're all surface.
他們都是曇花一現
They're fads.
他們不是這家報社成立的基礎
They aren't the foundation  this paper was built on,
他們也無法讓這家報社存活
and they aren't what will keep it alive.
我們的核心讀者  渴求紮實的新聞
We have a core readership  that thirsts for hard news.
我就是為這些人  一周工作80小時
Those are the people I work  80 hours a week for.
我不會受到流行的干擾
And I won't be distracted  by what's fashionable.
那是你的辭職信
That's your resignation letter.
出去時交給律師
Hand it to the lawyers on the way out.
我會給你些獨處時間
I'll give you some privacy.
不，留下，很快就好
No, no, stay, it'll be quick.
我們喝一杯吧
We'll get a drink.
我們要在華府這兒展開
We're gonna launch  right here in Washington.
當街頭滿是放羊的學童
We'll see how Congress likes it
看國會的反應如何
when the streets are teeming  with unsupervised school kids.
然後我們再逐步淘汰  全國其他區域
Then we'll phase out the rest of the country.
大家等我一分鐘，什麼事？
Everybody, hold on for one minute.  What's up?
- 國家教育協會出局了  - 什麼？
-The NEA is out.  -What?
- 他們退出了  - 為什麼？
-They pulled out.  -Why?
他不肯說
He wouldn't say.
再等我一分鐘
Hold on for one more minute.
恰克史羅恩？  馬上打電話給他
Chuck Sloan?  Get him on the phone right now.
我已連絡上他了
I've got him right here.
- 有靜音嗎？  - 有
-ls he muted?  -Yes.
恰克，我是馬帝
Hey, Chuck, it's Marty.
聽我說，你不能這樣做
Listen, you can't do this.
我們現在若不團結，就無法…
If we don't stay united now,  we don't have a...
你僱用我代表你的利益，對吧？
You hired me  to represent your interests, right?
若在聯合罷工前
How could I possibly lobby for the teachers
國會看到我們分裂  我要怎麼為教師遊說…
when Congress sees us splintering  before we even put up a unite...
好吧
All right.
安德沃找過你了？
Did Underwood get to you?
法蘭滿口謊言，善於操縱
Frank is dishonest and manipulative.
你知道他已經騙過我們
You've seen that he's lied to us already.
等等，恰克？恰克！
Wait, Chuck? Chuck, Chuck? Chuck!
他媽的！
Son of a bitch!
- 你在哪？  - 我在辦公室
-Where are you?  -I'm at the office.
- 騙人  - 你不相信我？
-False.  -You don't believe me?
完全不信
Not for a second.
你在哪？
Where are you?
- 正要去開會  - 和誰？
-About to walk into a meeting.  -With who?
一個我要懲罰的傢伙
Someone I have to punish.
告訴我名字
Give me a name.
無可奉告
No names.
這個人犯了什麼錯？
What did this person do wrong?
對我說謊
Lie to me.
你要怎麼懲罰他？
How will you punish him?
你為什麼覺得是個男人？
What makes you think it's a him?
等等，我得接個電話
Hold on. I have to take this.
- 你在哪？  - 我？我在…
-Where are you?  -Me? I am...
不在辦公室
Not at the office.
你打算每周都給我一個新手機？
You're gonna give me  a new one of these every week?
我無法繼續…
Well, I can't continue to...
要有保護措施
Not without protection.
沒人能管我何時工作、玩樂
Nobody tells me when to work  and when to play.
我不是無理要求，喬伊
I'm not being unreasonable, Zoe.
如果你不信任我  我們就不該這麼做
If you can't trust me,  we shouldn't be doing this at all.
那我們該如何建立信任？
Well, then how do we establish our trust?
我非常謹慎
I have been very discreet.
職業謹慎，對
Professional discretion, yes.
但這是你沒接觸過的領域
But this is new territory.
你的手機有鏡頭
You have a camera on your phone.
照吧
Pictures.
那種不能給爸爸看的照片
The kind I wouldn't want my father to see.
我要更曝露的
Well, I'm gonna need more than that.
躺下
Lie back.
發揮你的想像力
Use your imagination.
打包好一切，準備明天出發
I want everything packed for tomorrow.
爸爸，我們檢查過了
We checked already, Dad.
有嗎？廚房流理台上的  粉紅耐吉球鞋是我的嗎？
Did you? Those are my pink Nikes  on the kitchen counter?
還有你，汽車人  變形金剛怎麼會在我床底下？
And you, Autobot,  what is Optimus Prime doing under my bed?
在我們明天出發前
He better transform himself  into your backpack
他最好要變形到你的背包裏
before you have to leave tomorrow.
爸，克裏絲汀娜會回來嗎？
Hey, Dad, is Christina coming back?
我…應該不會，小子
I don't... I don't think so, buddy. No.
我喜歡她
I liked her.
我也是，她很棒
Me, too. She's cool.
對，她很棒
Yeah, she is cool.
你們得刷牙了  然後再檢查房間一遍
Now, you guys gotta brush your teeth.  And then check the rooms again.
接著就準備上床睡覺
And then it's time for bed.
南瓜，懂嗎？
Got it, pumpkins?
爸，你知道我最不喜歡  你叫我們南瓜
Dad, you know I hate it  when you call us pumpkins.
去吧，不然我把你們烤成南瓜派
Go. Before I turn you into a pie.
彼得魯索
Peter Russo.
第一選區彼得魯索
- 他是酒鬼  - 他現在是
-He's a drunk.  -He is at the moment.
他很能幹，想想他若戒酒
A very functional one.  Imagine if he was sober.
即便如此，你推他選州長  大家還是會挖他的過去
Even so, you run him for Governor,  people are going to dig into his past.
我們就轉劣勢為優勢
Well, we turn that into an asset,  not a liability.
今日之我非昨日之我
Here's who I was, here's who I am now.
你看到在領導會議上  大家三秒鐘就剔除他的名字了
You saw how they dismissed him  in three seconds at the Leadership meeting.
派翠惠特克心胸開闊  我又善於說服他人
Patti Whittaker is very open-minded.  And I am very persuasive.
你覺得魯索想嗎？
You think Russo even wants it?
能從南費城街道
Any kid who's made it  from the streets of South Philly
晉陞至國會大樓的人  莫不野心十足
to the Capitol rotunda is ambitious.
我們只需要激起這個野心
We just need to tap into that.
派給他最佳人才  再建立競選機制
Surround him with the best people  and then build the machine
就能一飛沖天
and push the "go" button.
所以你覺得他會贏
So you think he could win.
我覺得他能角逐得冠
I think he can be a contender.
好吧，假設我們製造了奇蹟  他贏了
Okay, let's say we pull off a miracle  and he wins.
有什麼好處？
What do we gain by it?
能掌控這場競選
Isn't it better  to be holding the reins in this race
不是好過當個旁觀者嗎？
than watching from the stands?
- 您的夫人打電話來  - 把電話轉過來
-Your wife is on the phone.  -Put her through in here.
我瞭解賓州  在重劃選區的重要性…
I understand that Pennsylvania's  important for re-districting...
道格，這不只是和這場競選有關
No, no, no,  this isn't just about this race, Doug.
把眼光放遠一點  還有誰是賓州人？
Expand your thinking.  Who else is from Pennsylvania?
國會並沒有
No, no, no, not in Congress.
行政部門
The executive branch.
副總統
The Vice President.
你好，親愛的
Hello, my dear.
南茜把我的燕尾服拿去乾洗  所以我不會…
Nancy had my tux dry-cleaned  so I won't embarrass...
克斯沃取消了訂位
The Cotesworth canceled on us.
我馬上出發去接你  我得走了
I'm leaving right now. I'll come get you.  I've gotta go.
怎麼了？
What's going on?
今晚辦藝廊的飯店
The hotel, for tonight's gala,
他們不讓克萊兒進去宴會廳  因為他們的員工是工會成員
they refuse to let Claire into the ballroom  because their employees are union.
史皮奈拉
Spinella.
他怎麼對付我無所謂  但動到我老婆身上？
Yeah, he can go after me all he wants.  But to go after my wife?
沒水準
No class.
- 到克斯沃飯店跟我會合  - 好的
-Meet me at the Cotesworth.  -You got it.
我們何不換到另一個場地？
Why can't we just move it to another place?
我查過，都被訂滿了
I looked into that. Everything's booked.
這得好幾周前事先預訂
You have to reserve these things  weeks in advance.
我請史坦普上網查別的場地
I got Stamper online  looking for another venue somewhere.
法蘭斯，送貨卡車  已經到克斯沃飯店了
Francis, the delivery trucks  are already at the Cotesworth.
我不能要大家去別的地方
I can't have people showing up  at a different place
以防他們沒接到通知
in case they don't get the email.
好吧，這是我的錯，真糟
All right. This is my fault. I feel awful.
這可是50萬啊
There's a half a million on the line here.
我明白
I realize that.
我不能一直讓我的工作  被你牽連
And I can't keep having my work  take these hits on behalf of yours.
這可不是小事
It's more than just an inconvenience.
我知道，我們會解決的
I know. We'll solve it.
- 我剛收到你的電郵  - 你覺得如何？
-Hey, I just got your email.  -What'd you think?
你發文前不需經過我同意
You don't have to send me things  before you post.
我以為你想看看
I thought you might want to take a look.
這裏的目的是讓大家
The goal here is for everyone
能在我讀之前就先發文
to post things faster  than I have a chance to read 'em.
如果你對文章滿意，儘管發文
If you're satisfied with the article,  you just put it up.
好吧
Okay.
- 你滿意嗎？  - 還可以吧
-Are you satisfied?  -I think so.
滿意還是不滿意
Okay, you are or you aren't.
不管《先軀報》是怎麼逼你的…
Whatever hoops The Herald  made you jump through...
- 我知道  - 就別管那套了
-I know.  -Let them go.
喬伊，這裏可以有個人主見
It's okay to be opinionated, Zoe.
也可以到外面挖新聞
And it's okay to go outside  and get your hands dirty.
你不需要被綁在桌前
You're no longer tied to a desk.
- 或是那個墊子  - 我不打算發這篇文
-Or to that pillow for that matter.  -I'm not gonna post it.
期中預測不是新聞，只是胡扯
Midterm predictions, they're not news.  They're bullshit.
我同意
Well, I agree.
- 我可以做得更好  - 我覺得你可以
-I can do better.  -I think you can.
隨時給我驚喜吧
Feel free to blow my mind.
如果我們辦這場活動  所有職員都會罷工
If we do this event, the whole staff walks out.
- 我有三百位貴賓…  - 你和我老婆簽了約
-I've got 300 guests...  -You signed a contract with my wife.
我們會將錢退回您老婆的機構  償付所有支出
We'll refund your wife's organization  and pay for whatever the cost of
將活動移至更適宜的場地舉辦
moving the event  to a more appropriate venue.
我們就得退回50萬的捐款
And we would have to refund  half a million dollars in donations.
你們也能支付嗎？
Can you pay for that, too?
我確信這是導致損害的原因
'Cause I'm pretty sure  there's cause for damages here.
我很抱歉，先生
I truly apologize, sir.
你的老闆是誰？
Who's your boss?
我和老闆談過
I spoke with the owners,
他們授權讓我做最佳決定
and they authorized me to do  what I think is best.
他們是否知道他們
And do they realize  that they are shutting the door
將41位美國國會議員  拒之於大門外嗎？
on 41 members of  the United States Congress?
是的，先生，他們知道
Yes, sir. They do.
我做了非常艱難的判斷
I had to make a very hard judgment call.
我嚴重質疑你的判斷力
Well, I seriously question your judgment.
你要知道，在這話傳得有多快
You know, word travels fast in this town.
所有午餐聚會、會議與晚宴
All those luncheons  and conventions and dinners,
這些生意全都沒了有多可惜
it's gonna be a shame  to lose all that work, isn't it?
議員，您說得對  但是若我的員工罷工，我…
Congressman, you are absolutely right,  but if my staff walks out, l...
請瞭解我所處的困境
Please understand the predicament I'm in.
我有個主意
I got an idea.
克斯沃飯店
我知道該怎麼做
I know what we're gonna do.
親愛的，他們不讓我們進去
Honey, they're not gonna  let us have it inside,
我們就在這裏  在他們前門階梯辦野餐會
we're gonna have it right here,  on their front steps. Picnic style.
- 你需要我幫什麼？  - 出人力
-What do you need from me?  -I need your manpower.
是的，議員，我明白
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
好了，各位  停下手邊工作聽我說
Okay, everybody,  stop what you're doing and listen up.
什麼事？
Yeah?
法蘭
Hey, Frank.
我要你幫我一個大忙
Listen, I need a favor, a large one.
多快？
How soon?
三小時之後
In about three hours.
- 多少人？  - 只有三百人
-How many people we talking?  -Just 300.
花店會送來所有的存貨
The florist is gonna send over  whatever he has.
很好
Great.
法蘭斯，食物呢？
Francis, where are we with food?
我訂了熱狗、披薩  和南方黑人食物
I've got hot dogs, pizzas,  and soul food coming.
或許還有別的
Maybe something else.
女孩們，我是這麼想的
Girls. Here's what I want.
我要弄四個吧檯、每邊兩個  食物放到那裏
I want four bars, two on each level.  The food can go there.
無聲拍賣在這邊辦
The silent auction goes here.
取消絃樂四重奏，找DJ來
And cancel the string quartet.  Let's get a DJ.
道格，酒如何？
Doug, how are we on booze?
- 酒桶快到了  - 好
-Kegs are on their way now.  -Great.
打電話到辦公室給丹妮絲
And call Denise at the office
叫她把所有  找得到的捐款信封都帶來
and have her bring  every donation envelope she can find.
訊息、人員
Okay, messages, people.
議員魯索辦公室  請稍候一分鐘，謝謝
Congressman Russo's office.  Yes, can you hold one minute? Thank you.
議員？大家不斷打電話  問造船廠的事
Congressman?  People keep calling about the shipyards.
我們不會回答
We don't know what to tell them.
只說會留言給您
We just say we'll give you the message.
- 繼續吧  - 好，這些是留言
-Keep saying that.  -Okay, here they are.
我們收到的留言與電郵
The messages and all the emails  we've gotten to.
您是否需要我…晚安
Do you want me to... Have a good night.
- 我們要連絡誰？  - 《先軀報》、  《時代》和《今日美國》
-Who'd we reach?  -Herald, The Times, USA Today.
還要電台和有線新聞
All right, I want affiliate stations  and cable news.
安排衛星轉播車  我要實況轉播這件事
I want satellite trucks out there.  I want this on live TV.
好，這就去辦
Okay, I'm on it.
你們不能在這辦
You can't do this here.
喬伊，今晚8點在克斯沃飯店
Zoe, 8:00 p.m. tonight, Hotel Cotesworth.
我老婆的慈善拍賣會
Benefit for my wife's charity.
不，臉洗乾淨，頭發放下
No. Wash your face and let your hair down.
這是工作也是娛樂
This is work and play.
等會見
See you.
我現在就告訴你，我要兩打
I can tell you right now  I'm gonna need two dozen.
保羅，我明天就要，好嗎？
Paul, I'm gonna need those  by tomorrow, okay?
你們的客人是你們的問題  不是我的
Your guests are your problem, not mine.
- 朱利安  - 我會關大門
-Julian.  -I'll close the gate.
我不是消防法規專家
You know, I'm no expert in fire code,
但是我可以想像  將客人關在裏面
but I would imagine  that locking your guests in
比讓他們在我們身邊  自由走動更違法
is a bigger violation  than having them walk around us.
這是侵犯私人財產  你們是違法的
This is trespassing on private property.  You're breaking the law.
好吧，行
All right. Okay.
我幫你打電話給邦尼霍爾
Let me get Barney Hull on the phone  here for you.
好，電話響了
Here you go. It's ringing.
- 邦尼霍爾是誰？  - 警察局長
-Who's Barney Hull?  -Police Commissioner.
- 警察局長辦公室，你好  - 不要？好吧
-Commissioner Hull's office. Hello?  -No? Okay.
你想和他當面談？  很好，他會來參加派對
You'd rather talk to him in person?  That's great. He's coming to the party.
我一定會介紹你們認識  感謝你的款待
I'll be sure to introduce the two of you.  Thanks for your hospitality.
你要我怎麼做？我不能鎖大門
What do you want me to do?  I can't lock the gates.
警方又站在他們那邊
And they've got the police on their side.
真不敢相信，等等
Unbelievable. Hold on.
卡珊德拉，我要兩百位教師  現在就到克斯沃飯店
Cassandra. I need 200 teachers  at the Cotesworth Hotel. Right now.
- 我要大規模示威  - 兩百？我不知能不能
-I need a full picket.  -Two hundred? I don't know if we can
- 找到那麼多…  - 我不想聽，去做就是了
-get that many on...  -I don't want to hear it. Just get it done.
坦白說，是不是教師無所謂
All right. I don't give a fuck  if they're teachers or not, frankly.
給我找到兩百人
Just get me 200 bodies.
打電話給貨運聯盟  或許他們能幫忙
Call the Teamsters, maybe they'll help us.
如果有必要，就給他們眼鏡  叫他們打扮好一點
We'll give them glasses if we have to.  Tell the guys to look smart.
查理，掛掉電話  我要一百個以上的標語牌
Charlie, get off the phone.  I need signs right now, at least 100.
就讓他們去吧
You know what? Let them set it up.
這樣對我們更好，他們…  他們就無法躲過我們
It's actually better for us that way. They...  This way they can't hide from us.
你讓我陷於窘境
You've put me in a terrible situation.
非常感謝你的協助
Thank you very much for all your help.
感激不盡
Much appreciated.
這裏，這裏有標語牌  快點發出去
Here, we've got the signs right here.  Let's hand them out fast.
各位，沿著這條街排成一排  這邊和那邊，好嗎？
Everybody, single file, right down the street,  this way and that way, okay?
法蘭安德沃
至少他拼對了名字
Well, at least he spelled it right.
抗議教育改革與成就法案的教師
Teachers protesting the Education Reform  and Achievement Act
聚集於華府的克斯沃飯店
have descended upon the Hotel Cotesworth  in Washington, D. C.
教師工會抗議
淨水創權不顧抗議  藝廊持續進行
工會陳情代表  馬帝史皮奈拉發起示威
Union lobbyist, Marty Spinella,  organized the demonstration.
尊重教師！
Teachers deserve respect!
我就知道  你會帶美麗的老婆來參加
Now, I knew you'd show up  and you'd bring that beautiful wife of yours.
你好，幸會，感謝大駕光臨
Hello, it's a pleasure, thank you for coming.
進來吧，飲料免費
Come on in, the drinks are on the house.
- 費莉絲  - 派對可以開始了
-Felicity.  -The party can begin.
是史皮奈拉
This is Spinella.
他讓我們被工會拒之於外
He got us shut out by the union,
我們只好在階梯上辦派對
so we had to have a party  out here on the steps.
我現在就帶你去吧檯
I'm gonna take you up to a bar right now.
謝謝光臨，歡迎
Thank you for coming. Thank you. Welcome.
教師萬歲！工會萬歲！
Teachers, yes! Unions, yes!
你好
Hi.
再次感謝大駕光臨
Thanks, again, so much for coming.
亞當來了
Adam's here.
你來了
You came.
看起來很棒
Looks wonderful.
麻煩讓開一下
You're gonna have to move over
我得親自服務  這對了不起的夫妻
because I have to  serve this wonderful couple myself.
這個主意真棒  只有克萊兒想得出來
This is fabulous.  Only Claire could have thought of this.
有純麥芽酒嗎？
I don't suppose  you have anything single-malt back there?
法蘭，看你當酒保就值回票價了
Frank, it's worth every penny  to see you on keg duty.
你們不覺得這值得更高價嗎？
Well then, don't you think  that this is worth just a few extra pennies?
查理，我們該拿支票簿出來了
Let's break out the checkbook, Charles.
你有回覆參加嗎？
Did you RSVP?
我想這無所謂吧
I assumed it didn't matter.
當然無所謂
It doesn't.
我很高興你來
I'm glad you're here.
我聽到你的留言時…
When I heard your message...
我不該留言的，亞當
You know, I shouldn't have left that, Adam.
為什麼？
Why not?
或許我們該找時間談談
Maybe we should talk at some point.
可以後面多加幾個零嗎？
Make that check  with a lot of zeros, won't you?
拿去吧
Here we are.
- 乾杯  - 乾杯
-Cheers.  -Cheers.
乾杯
Cheers.
既然你都來了  我得請你幫個大忙
Now I'm going to ask a huge favor of you  since you're here.
- 你要我去當招待  - 對，拜託
-You want to put me to work.  -Yes, please.
- 我的榮幸  - 來吧
-My pleasure.  -Come.
這些精彩照片出自  一位優秀攝影師之手…
So these are some wonderful photographs  by an amazing photographer...
吉莉安…
Gillian...
- 亞當蓋羅威，幸會  - 久仰大名
-Adam Galloway. Nice to meet you.  -I've heard lots about you. And to you.
- 這是攝影師本人  - 你好
-And this is the photographer himself.  -Hello, how are you?
弗萊迪
Freddy.
我只是想對你致謝  今晚真是太棒了
I just wanted to thank you so much.  Such a success tonight.
- 我的榮幸  - 他最棒了
-My pleasure, my pleasure.  -He's the best.
- 我看到亞當來了  - 我不知道他會來
-I see Adam's here.  -I didn't know he was coming.
猜猜我拿到什麼  霍本夫婦又開了一張支票
Well, guess what I got.  Another check from the Holburns.
六萬
For $60,000.
讚美我吧
Come on, praise me like you should.
若法蘭安德沃和國會…
If Frank Underwood  and the United States Congress...
你好，我是喬伊邦斯  《頭條報導》
Hi, my name is Zoe Barnes. I'm with Slugline.
…以為可以廢除美國教師的權利
...think that they can dismantle the rights of  the American teacher,
那他們會隨時隨地  聽到我們的抗議之聲
well, then they are going to  hear our voices wherever they are.
你好，為何在此抗議？
Hi, why protest here?
國會必須認真看待此事
Congress has to take this seriously.
我們是為教師而來…
We're here for the teachers. We're here...
謝謝
Thank you. Thank you.
我們的要求並不過分
We're not asking for the world.
國會必須站出來解決這件事
And Congress needs to step up  and get this done.
抱歉，失陪
Excuse me, just a moment.
這件洋裝很眼熟
Well, that dress looks familiar.
我穿這件去聽交響樂的
It's the one I wore to the symphony.
對，攀高附貴
Yes, the mutual admiration society.
沒錯
That's right.
你要給我什麼？
So. What do you have for me?
什麼意思？
What do you mean?
你周圍儘是華府名流
Well, you're surrounded  by Washington's elite.
你難道沒聽到  對我們有用的消息？
Are you saying you've overheard nothing  that could be useful to either of us?
我是來報導抗議的
I'm covering the protest.
全世界都在報導這個抗議
The rest of the world is covering the protest.
你可能沒注意到
You may not have noticed,
但你可是派對裏唯一的記者
but you're the only journalist  inside the party.
邦斯小姐，我幫了你許多  消息該是互通的
I've been feeding you plenty,  information is a two-way street, Ms. Barnes.
你好…
Hello...
克萊兒，這是喬伊邦斯  那晚在家裏見過…
Claire, this is Zoe Barnes,  you met her one night at the house...
我記得  你在《先軀報》上班，對吧？
Yes, I remember.  You work for The Herald, right?
我離開了  現在為《頭條報導》工作
Not anymore. I actually work at Slugline now.
我聽說過  法蘭斯，你有讀過吧？
I've heard of it.  You read it, don't you, Francis?
非常忠實
Religiously.
你看起來年輕上進，我很欣賞
Well, you seem like  a very ambitious young woman. I like that.
我盡力而為
Doing my best.
真的很高興再見到你
It's good to see you, again.
- 盡情享樂  - 我會的，謝謝
-Please, enjoy yourself.  -I will. Thank you.
邦斯小姐，保重
Take care, Ms. Barnes.
我現在一無所有  你讓我和我的孩子
流落街頭  你這王八蛋叛徒
你耍我是為了什麼？  我要知道
魯索，吃屎吧
去你的，可恥
你是好人還是我看錯人了？  你能幫我嗎？
誠摯的  蘇珊喬治
親愛的蘇珊  我知道你不好受
我知道你怪我
你不是唯一怪我的人
你沒看錯人
我是好人
至少我試著要當好人
造船廠必須關閉
是因為
是因為我這回無法對抗
這回
她看起來真美
And she looks gorgeous,
但其實她在想  「我何時能回家？」
but really she's thinking,  "When can I go the fuck home?"
- 我要走了  - 現在？
-I'm off.  -Already?
我想我已盡了我的職責
I've done my duty, I believe.
你瞭解我  我向來是第一個離開派對的人
You know me.  I always have to be the first to leave a party.
你募集了多少錢？
How much did you raise?
75萬
$750,000.
- 八萬是從你的照片募來的  - 太好了
-Eighty of that was your photographs.  -Fantastic.
再來一張25萬支票  我們就破百萬了
Write a check for 250, we'll break a million.
幹得好
Nice try.
謝謝參加  謝謝你所做的一切
Thank you for coming.  And everything that you did.
有空連絡我
Call me sometime.
我會的
I will.
善待教師！
Teachers should be getting more!
淨水藝廊與教師工會有何關連？
So what does a Clean Water gala  have to do with teachers unions?
50多位國會議員聚集於此
Well, we have over 50 members  of Congress gathered in one place.
但是這些國會議員
But the fact that these members of Congress
拚命將錢丟到國外
are promoting pouring money  out of the country
忽視國內教師  這就是問題所在
while neglecting their teachers at home  is precisely the problem.
但這是私人款項  不是納稅人的錢…
But this is private money,  not public tax dollars, so...
但是我們不是抗議活動本身
But we're not protesting the cause,
而是抗議國會議員和女性…
we're protesting the Congressmen  and women themselves...
這些示威的人是教師嗎？
Are these even teachers picketing?
當然，部分是教師，部分是…
Sure, some of them.  And some of them are people...
抱歉…
Excuse me...
法蘭…你是…別拿食物  我們等一下會發食物
Frank... What you... Don't take the food.  We'll feed you later.
- 別拿食物  - 馬帝，你知道一句老話
-Don't take this food.  -Marty, you know that old saying,
「世上最危險之處  就在貨運聯盟與免費食物之間」
"The most dangerous spot in the world is  to come between a Teamster and free food."
別拿食物  我們等一下會發食物
Don't take the food, we're feeding you later.
- 我要拿  - 她要拿
-I'll take it.  -She'll take it.
還有誰餓了？
Who else is hungry?
拿去吧
There you go.
請傳過去
Pass it back.
還有更多食物
Plenty more coming, guys.
我知道你們站在這裏好久了
I know you've all been out here for hours.
謝謝，弗萊迪
Thank you, Freddy!
華府最棒的肋排
The best ribs in D.C.
馬帝，來吧  你說了觀點，上了新聞
Marty, come on.  You've said your piece, you got on the news.
來吃吧
Come and enjoy yourself.
克萊兒，我尊重你  你知道我不能
I respect you, Claire,  you know I can't do that.
你們支持哪邊都無所謂  大家都得吃
Doesn't matter what side you're on,  everybody's gotta eat.
你可以吃一盤肋排
You can have a plate of ribs. Yes, you can.
- 來吧，行的  - 我不行
-Come on. Yes, you can.  -I can't.
- 謝謝，克萊兒，但我不行  - 行的
-Thank you, Claire, but I cannot.  -You can do it.
- 來吧，馬帝！來吧  - 我不行，謝謝
-Come on, Marty! Come on.  -I can't. Thank you. Thank you.
弗萊迪餐館  去弗萊迪餐館吃吧
Freddy's. You should go to Freddy's.
教師抗議  淨水創權藝廊
抗議者為肋排不顧勸說
勞工陳情代表馬帝史皮奈拉  領導數十位工會支持者
Several dozen union sympathizers,  led by labor lobbyist, Martin Spinella,
試圖打斷藝廊
attempted to disrupt the gala.
他們得採取行動  關懷教師與孩子
They need to step up to the plate and  take care of our teachers and our children.
當參加募款的人  發送食物飲料給抗議者時
The protest dissipated  when fundraiser attendees
抗議也不了了之
offer food and drink to picketers.
你們支持哪邊都無所謂  大家都得吃
Doesn't matter what side you're on,  everybody's gotta eat.
關掉
T urn it off.
不清楚是否會持續抗議
It's unclear  whether protest will continue.
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
打電話給工會領袖  和各分會主席
Call the union leadership  and the chapter presidents.
看他們是否準備展開罷工  若準備好了，明天午夜就罷工
See if they're ready to the pull the trigger.  If they are, we strike at midnight tomorrow.
你太棒了
You were extraordinary.
今晚沒來的人  明天都會謊稱有來參加
Tomorrow, people who weren't there  are gonna lie and say they were.
你在讀什麼？
What are you reading?
淨水沖掉工會
她真能寫
She can write.
是啊
She can.
而你很會募款
And you can raise money.
只為了正當目的
Always, for a good cause.
謝謝
Thank you.
請在車內等待
Wait in the car, please.
等等，我知道那是誰
Hold on. I know who that is.
你好，彼得
Hello, Peter.
我好餓，我忘了吃飯
I am starving. I forgot to eat.
- 彼得，你要吃點什麼嗎？  - 不了，謝謝
-Would you like something, Peter?  -No, thanks.
你該吃點
You should eat.
- 別和她爭，她穩贏的  - 好吧
-Don't fight. She'll win.  -I will.
好的
Okay, yes.
- 來點咖啡？  - 好，謝謝
-You want some coffee?  -Yes, thanks.
你有孩子嗎？
Do you have any children?
兩個，一男一女
Two. A son and a daughter.
已婚？
Married?
離婚了
Divorced.
你的孩子叫什麼名字？
What are their names, your kids?
莎拉11歲，凱文八歲
There's Sarah. She's 1 1, and Kevin is eight.
你有照片嗎？
Do you have any pictures?
可惡！
Fuck!
我掉了手機…
I lost my phone...
抱歉，我得…我得走了…
Sorry, I should... I gotta go...
彼得，坐下
Peter, sit down.
吃三明治，喝點咖啡  在這裏過夜吧
You're gonna enjoy your sandwich,  have some coffee and stay the night.
牛奶和糖？
Milk and sugar?
黑咖啡
Black.
乾淨毛巾
Some fresh towels.
浴室有香皂、牙膏  和其他必需品
There should be soap and toothpaste,  everything you need in the bathroom.
非常謝謝你
Thank you so much for doing this.
不客氣，好好睡
It's nothing. Sleep well.
彼得，怎麼了？
What's going on, Peter?
告訴我
Talk to me.
你以為乾淨毛巾能改變什麼嗎？
You think fresh towels changes anything?
改變什麼？
Changes what?
造船廠
The shipyard.
如果你在我老家搞那種事  我絕對海扁你
If I was home and you pulled that shit,  I'd beat the fuck out ofyou.
我會在人行道上打碎你的腦袋
I would crack your skull on the pavement.
這就是我今天來的目的
That's why I came over here today.
為你逼我做的事海扁你
To fuck you up for what you made me do.
我才不管你對我多好
I don't care how nice you're being to me.
我才不鳥你
I don't give a shit.
明天我起床時
I'm gonna wake up tomorrow,
這些人
and all these people,
我所有的朋友
all my friends,
還是一團糟
are still fucked.
我還是一團糟
And I'm still fucked.
你耍了我們全部人
You fucked all of us.
但我卻是代罪羔羊
But I'm gonna get blamed for it.
現在我得肩負重責
So, now I have to carry that weight  on my shoulders.
法蘭，你耍了我
You fucked me, Frank.
我不該讓你這麼做的  但是我…
I shouldn't have let you do it, but I did...
你說完了嗎？
Are you done now?
起來
Get up.
不要
No.
我說起來，跟我過來
I said get up. And follow me.
現在
Now.
進去
Get in.
脫掉你的衣服進去
Take off your clothes and get in.
現在就脫
Do it. Now.
這周稍早開了民主黨全委會會議  討論州長競選
There was a DNC meeting earlier this week.  About the Governor's race.
你的名字出現在  我們可能找來競選的名單
Your name came up  as someone we might want to run.
阿斯匹林，吃吧
Aspirin. Go ahead.
會議室所有人  都想把你的名字劃掉
Everyone in that room  wanted to cross you off the list.
我否決，支持你
I said no. I stuck up for you.
我說：  「彼得魯索有潛力
I said, "Peter Russo, he's got potential.
「他年輕能幹，大有前途」
"He's young, he's capable,  he's going places."
我說服他們繼續考慮你
I made them keep you in contention.
你還在名單上
You're still on that list.
你卻在半夜  醉醺醺地跑來我家抱怨？
You show up at my house  in the middle of the night, drunk, to whine?
還想反過來怪我？
To try to shift the blame on me?
卻不為你自己  和你自身的行為負責？
Instead oftaking responsibility  for yourself and your own actions?
或許他們說得對
Maybe they were right in that meeting.
或許你就是沒用
Maybe you are worthless.
我是唯一相信你的人  彼得，但是或許我錯了
I'm the only person who believes in you,  Peter, but maybe that's one too many.
熱水會擴散你的毛細孔
The hot water will open up your capillaries.
你剛吃的阿斯匹林  會讓你的血液較淡
The aspirin you just took  will make your blood thinner.
彼得，就看你的決定…
It's up to you, Peter...
如果你決定要當懦夫
And if you do decide  to take the coward's way out,
沿著血管切，不要橫著切  那是很低級的錯誤
cut along the tracks, not across them.  That's a rookie mistake.
- 早安  - 早安
-Morning.  -Morning.
要搭便車到國會嗎？
You need a lift to the Hill?
我得回家換衣服
I should go home and change my clothes.
不，我們載你去
No, no, we'll drop you.
喝點咖啡？
You want some coffee?
法蘭？
Frank?
一個月
One month.
一個月戒酒
One month sober.
我能對你保證
I can give you that.
不是對我，而是對你
Not for me. For you.
他打定主意了嗎？
Has the seed been planted?
只有彼得能回答那個問題
Only Peter can answer that question.
決定權在於他
He has a choice.
他會委靡不振？
Will he wither?
還是會重振旗鼓？
Or will he thrive?
只有時間能證明
Only time will tell.